We've kept men off this island for
centuries, excluding a slip-up or two.
To think that those barbarians
would invade us now.
They cut out a whole chunk of the
mountain and the town was heavily damaged.
As long as I'm here, the
navy will keep coming back.
Where should I go?
Oh, at times like this.
I just want to marry Luffy.
Don't you always want that?
The gate's been destroyed!
Don't let up yet.
Not till we send him to
the bottom of the sea.
Deploy the pacifistas. Immediately.
Seraphim, go.
Activate the camera.
We need to record this battle.
Roger that.
Still not coming out to fight, Hancock.
A warship is approaching!
from 6 o 'clock!
It's a pirate ship! This
is mad! What happened?
They're back here in the city!
Black Moon's attacking!
Everyone hold on!
It's a sea plane!
It's gonna anger the Sea Kings!
Is that a child?
We can't fight a little girl!
How she's so strong?
And look at her.
I don't understand.
Oh, Pirate Empress, come out to play.
We came for a visit and to
take your Devil Fruit power.
Oh, Hancock, what a
gorgeous face you have.
I would love to take your head
and keep it as a treasure.
As long as I get her power, you
can do whatever the hell you want.
Well, if that's the case, don't
chop her head off right away.
Let's take her alive and we
can have some fun with her.
Blackbeard, that's as far as you go.
Vice Admiral, sir, we've
made contact with Blackbeard.
Give the order to attack.
Wait for HQ's approval.
Carlike.
Stay out of my way!
Hancock, get your ass out here!
Blackbeard is here? I see.
I suppose there are plenty
of reasons why pirates
like him would want to
target the former warlords.
We'll never gain any ground like this.
Watch out!
Thanks for that. Anytime.
Now let's hurry up and take care of this
before there are any more casualties.
Hancock!
The Navy does not desire a
fight with you or your people.
If we can take you into custody,
then we will withdraw immediately.
Don't push your luck.
Kobe the hero.
We'll handle him, sister. Stay inside.
Don't be absurd.
They can't capture me.
No one can.
I will never bow to the likes of them.
Don't do this.
Let us protect you.
Commodore Dash!
Nothing's working on this guy!
Are you kidding me?
You all got your asses kicked
for that one little shrimp?
Wait, that kid.
He's got white hair, brown
skin, and black wings.
P-X?
It can't be!
He's a pacifista!
Airman, pacifist a brat, I'll kill him!
Where the hell is he?
He's small, but his arm...
is huge.
All right, then.
Let's go!
Whoa, man.
This isn't looking good.
Oh, wee!
Why, hello there, lovely.
Even the Blackbeard Pirates are affected.
Slave Ow!
This is a mess.
We've got to stop her quick, Helmepo.
Helmepo, no!
The Vice Admiral, too?
Pacifistas, stand down!
They'll break all of the
people who are petrified!
Pacifistas!
This is an order!
Stop attacking!
So that's Kobe.
Perfume!
She's too fast!
Black Vortex!
Like that stopped you dead in your tracks.
This is darkness.
It absorbs all Devil Fruit powers.
Snake Princess! What happened?
She can't use her power anymore?
You're disgusting.
Unhand me at once.
I should have known the pirate empress
wouldn't give up without a fight.
You certainly did a
number on my crewmates.
Turned those idiots to stone
the second they showed up.
I knew she was tough, but this
is beyond anything I imagined.
What should I do?
That power of yours, I think it's
going to serve me quite nicely.
Do as you will, but my power
is useless without my beauty.
And if you kill me, your
crewmates will remain petrified.
The next wielder cannot
undo the damage I've done.
We're not getting anywhere, are we?
Help me out, Kobe.
You did me a real favor last time we met.
You were my hero at Rocky Port 2.
I've been on a roll thanks to you.
I was able to take down Wong Z.
And now, Pirate Island is
my personal playground.
Well, what do you think?
Make the call if I take my hands
off her like she requested.
Do you think she'll keep her word?
Will she have any incentive to turn
my crewmates back if she's free?
She needs to turn back everyone here
who was petrified, marines included.
I don't want to fight.
You, if you leave, I'll set them all free.
Do we have a deal?
Hell, no!
You're a liar.
As soon as I let you go, you'll
turn everyone here into a statue.
We'll be dead, just like that!
Am I wrong?
As you've said, you're quite the beauty.
No one who sets eyes on you can resist
your power, no matter how strong you are.
So, what to do?
Safer to just kill you!
Don't do this, Blackbeard!
Think of how many lives
we'll be lost if she dies!
I knew the Navy would attack eventually,
but I never imagined they'd
cut a hole out the island,
sorry
to make you wait, Hancock!
I'm here now.
As for you,
don't test my patience any further!
I never did like you,
Whitebeard's cabin boy!
Let's make this
Quick!
Listen Hancock turn
everyone back to normal.
I'll keep your enemies in check
None of you try anything foolish.
Leave this island in peace.
I'm glad you're still alive.
Dangerous times we're living in, huh?
We owe you our lives, Rayleigh. Thank you.
New technology makes for new threats
What happens now?
With those paddle ships,
the Calm Belt's not safe.
I hope Vegapunk is happy with
the inconveniences caused us.
The Navy launches a siege.
Those strange new weapons attack.
Then Blackbeard comes for our Empress.
I don't know what we would
have done without your aid.
I can't take much credit.
I couldn't have helped under
different circumstances.
I hate to say it, but I'm not a young man.
I can't hope to defeat Blackbeard.
Not in his current state.
This could have been much worse.
Those weapons, the strange children.
It seems they're quite powerful.
To think the Navy would replace
the seven warlords with machines.
They must be confident in them.
As well they should be, I must admit.
We couldn't even put a scratch
on those wretched little beasts.
But that wasn't the strangest part.
I swear, one of them looked just like
Hancock did when she was a child.
Yes, sir, we'll proceed to
egghead and dock the ship.
As for Captain Kobe, I'm
afraid the news is true.
Captain Kobe,
the hero from the Rocky Port incident
was abducted by Blackbeard, the Emperor?
of the sea.
His fate, unknown.
It's a lie!
I know it is!
Slave would never kill me again!
This has got to be some kind
of setup, I'm telling you!
Yes, I agree.
It doesn't hold up under scrutiny.
The Revolutionary Army is
opposed to the world nobles.
Kings like Cobra aren't their enemy.
The Revolutionary Army declared
war on the Celestial Dragons.
The Chief of Staff Sabo
assassinated King Cobra of Alabasta.
There it is. Wait.
His daughter Vivi, the Princess
of Alabasta, disappeared?
Oh, Vivi!
If only I could be there
to comfort you right now!
I hope you're okay!
I say we should go to Alabasta!
Turn the ship around!
The King's already dead.
It's too late for us to help.
And what will we even do there?
We don't have any leads on Vivi either.
They lost track of her and Marie Joie.
Then go there!
Head to Marie Joie! What? No.
Surely I must have misheard him, right?
Even there, not that crazy.
I can't hear a damn thing in here!
That's the enemy's stronghold.
We can't just march in there.
You want to pick a fight with Navy HQ?
Why not, huh? What's wrong?
You scared, Zoro?
We don't have a damn thing to go
off Calm the hell down, would you?
Phoebe's dad is dead?
That's horrible!
Even though we're a bunch of
pirates, he was so nice to all of us!
I am grateful from the bottom of my heart
as a father and a native of this land.
Alabasta will forever be
in your dead Straw Hats.
Thank you all very much.
He was the best king in the whole
world Why did he have to die? Vivi!
I'm so worried.
She must be going through so much.
I hope she's okay.
Oh Vivi!
Vivi!
Seems the reverie was quite tumultuous.
It's a shame she got wrapped up in it.
I simply can't imagine
why the revolutionary
army would want to target Alabasta's king.
Hold up a second.
We met the Sabo guy, didn't we?
When was that?
Oh, he came to dress Rosa.
That was when you last saw your bro.
Right, Luffy?
No, Vivi, where did you go?
I need to come for you. Me too.
Come on, we'll rescue her. Rescue!
Yeah!
All of you need to knock it off.
Stop screaming and focus.
Come on, Luffy.
You remember what you said two
years ago when Ace was in trouble?
Ace's adventures are his
own business, good or bad.
You trusted your brother.
You let him fight his own
battles till it got ugly.
You don't think Vivi's weak, do you?
Because I thought she was
pretty smart and tough, too.
When it comes time for us to fight,
we won't back down from any challenge,
but we can't do anything now, so shut up.
If all we can do is yell, let us yell!
Go back to Onigashima!
You're evil!
You green Kaido!
You big green mom!
Mosshead sucks! Boo!
Boo! Boo! Boo!
Shut up, fourth place.
Don't you dare?
I have to take charge
since I outranked you.
So you think you're
better than me, hot, yeah?
I always have been and I always will be.
There's so much to catch up on apparently,
the whole world turned
upside down while we were in.
A lot has changed, and more
change appears to be on the way.
The seven warlords might become an issue.
They're running wild after the
government shut the system down.
For example, three of them came
together to form Cross Guild.
As a result, Buggy was apparently crowned
one of the new four emperors of the sea.
There's no way that story is true!
We can't confirm it ourselves yet.
But for the time being,
it's the only truth we have.
Thank you, Brooke.
By the way, I noticed a few
more names you might recognize.
Would you like to hear the stories?
What do you think?
I'll leave that choice to you.
Just tell me if there's
anything big. All right.
It can wait, then.
I think you've got enough on your mind.
Anyway, Sabo's innocent.
When he was little, his parents
were always strict with him.
He just wants everyone to be free.
The three of us, we're
gonna leave this country.
We're gonna sail the
seas and see the world.
And once I've done it all, I'm going
to write a book for kids like me!
Because studying is fun when
you're learning about adventure,
and we're going to have lots of them!
We're going to be pirates!
You don't got to tell me.
I'm going to be a pirate anyway.
I'll be so tough that all the other pirates
and all the marines will bow at my feet.
Everyone in the world will know my name.
That's going to be the legacy
I leave behind when I die.
I don't care if people hate me.
I don't care if they
wish I'd never been born.
But they won't ignore me.
That's what it means to be
strong, to be a great pirate.
I won't ever lose and
I won't ever run away.
Who cares if the world fears
me or respects me or whatever.
I'm going to be a legend.
We made an oath.
Sabo, me, and Ace together.
Then I know what I'm gonna do, too!
Someday I...
Huh?
Wait, what did you just say? Huh?
You certainly know how to entertain,
don't you? Hold on. No, no. No way.
That's too crazy.
I love it.
I think that's perfect, Captain.
Hey, Chopper, might want
to examine his head.
Oh, come on.
That is impossible and you know it.
Maybe it'll be possible once
I'm King of the Pirates.
No one but you would think of
something like that, Luffy.
second I didn't tell you guys
this before none of you whatever
it won't happen anyway so I don't
care no I told ace and Sabo and
Shanks for sure what did they
say were they happy they were
laughing so I guess so I remember where
Shanks had tears in his eyes, too.
But that's what I want
at the end of my dream.
Thank you.
Oh, let's do it again, Flyer!